Right, that's all for today's class.
Remember, you'll be studying
for college exams next year,
"Katagiri High School"
Remember, you'll be studying
for college exams next year,
so you won't get to enjoy
your next summer vacation.
Go out and enjoy the pool
or the beach while you still can.
I'd be happy to go with you.
What? Why the hell would we
invite a teacher to come with us?
Oh, please, Ishikawa!
There's no point in going to the
pool or beach with a bunch of guys.
Oh, right.
God, they're so dumb.
Yasuda's pretty hot, but he
keeps opening his dumb mouth.
He's a good teacher, too.
Ugh, just ignore him.
Why? Did something happen
between you and Yasuda-sensei, Hori?
Yeah, this morning.
Hori! Keep your chin up, okay?
What? Why?
Here's a little-known fact about me:
I love flat-chested girls!
So have a little self-confidence!
That's how he tried to cheer me up.
Sorry. I have no idea what
he was trying to do there.
Oh, hey, Hori!
A guy from another school
asked me for your number.
Can I give it to him?
He didn't have the guts to ask
me himself, so no. Turn him down.
Aww, again?
Yo, wanna hit up karaoke on our way home?
Karaoke?
I got these coupons that expire today.
Half off two hours! That's a sweet deal!
Wanna go, Hori?
C'mon!
Sorry, I gotta pass.
You always pass!
I'm really sorry!
Hori-san.
Huh?
You dropped your phone.
Oh, thanks.
God, Miyamura sounds so gloomy.
Same as always, I guess.
I bet he's a total otaku.
Oh, I like this angle!
The "so moe!" kind?
Oh, yeah, totally!
What's he really like, Toru?
Don't really know.
Doesn't seem like he has
any friends we could ask, either.
Sorry, gotta run!
Hori's always in a hurry to get home.
It's probably because she's
got a boyfriend or something.
A boyfriend?!
I mean, she's pretty and popular.
I wouldn't be surprised.
Okay!
Hey, Mom.
Got it, I'll handle dinner.
I know, no getting out of overtime.
Bye.
I'd better get going...
"Lion Room"
Sota!
Big sis!
There you are!
"Karaoke"
I know, right?
Wanna hit up that store
we saw in that fashion mag?
Wait, like, now?!
Yeah, let's go!
Let's have hamburg steak for dinner tonight.
Yay!
"Horimiya"
"A Tiny Happenstance"
Overtime and working on her day off...
I really wish she'd learn to say no to people...
Big sis!
What's wrong?
"Bleed"
Sota! What happened?!
I fell down.
Aww. Where's your handkerchief, buddy?
U-Uhh...
Huh?!
I think he's okay now, so I'm gonna go.
I was totally ignoring him!
U-Uhh, I'm so sorry you
had to take care of him...
It's okay.
I'm gonna go, then.
Sota?
Uh, umm...
Umm, if you're not in a hurry,
why don't you come in for a few?
O-Okay, but...
Please. I have to thank you
for taking care of him.
He got scared by a dog and fell down.
Thank you for going so far out of your way.
Oh, no, thank you for treating me.
Hey, is your coffee really bitter?
It sure is.
He's a good kid.
Introduced himself and everything.
O-Oh, thank you. He's a real
handful most of the time, I swear.
Still, I'm really impressed that
you take care of all the housework.
I never expected that from you, Hori-san.
Oh, no...
You are Hori-san, right? In Class 1?
Y-Yeah, that's me,
but wait, you go to my school?!
Huh? What are you talking about?
I'm in your class. Miyamura?
Wait... What?!
That can't be the same person!
I still don't believe it.
Hori, you're making the
weirdest face right now. You okay?
Yeah, it's nothing.
You sure?
Huh? Hori?
Miyamura, can I have a sec?
Huh? You want me to come over again?
N-Not me! My little brother!
Sota wants 'that cool dude'
to come play with him.
Really? Then I'll pick up
a picture book for him or something.
It's fine. You don't have to
go out of your way or anything.
Whew, okay. Sota'll be really thrilled.
This is a surprise.
What is?
You talking to me.
I thought for sure after yesterday,
you'd just avoid being around me.
Why would I do that?
I mean, yeah, it was a little
awkward and freaked me out a bit.
You're so not like that here at school.
But I'm kinda in the same boat,
so I don't really have
a reason to avoid you or any...
Why're you blushing?
Uh, I guess I'm just not
used to hearing this stuff...
It's kinda weird.
But thanks.
What?
You've got a nice smile.
Huh?!
You should wear your hair up more often.
And lose the glasses, too.
I could, but then they'd see I have piercings.
You've got a lot, too. How many?
Nine, I think. Four on
each ear and one on my lip.
That's way too many piercings.
My mom said the same thing.
Here are a few things I've
learned about Miyamura so far:
I like manga, but I'm not
into all that moe stuff.
He's not an otaku.
I brought some cake!
His family runs a cake shop.
Yeah, it hurt a lot when I did it.
He pierced himself with
a safety pin back in middle school.
And...
Oof...
He's not a very good student.
You're incredible, Hori-san!
You've got almost straight A's!
It's nothing special.
Aren't quiet guys with
glasses supposed to be smart?
Is that how it works?
"This Week's Sales"
It's times like these when I realize
that my initial impression
of him was totally off the mark.
What's that? An ad for the supermarket?
Yeah.
Eggs are on sale tomo--
His lower eyelashes are really long.
Hori-san?
Oh, uh!
There's a limited-time sale on eggs
tomorrow with no purchase limit.
But it says "only until 4 PM."
Yeah, but it'll be fine.
As long as there's no emergency
committee meeting or anything,
I'll be able to buy a whole truckload
of eggs on my way home!
All committee members,
please report to the AV room after homeroom.
What great timing...
But I'm not giving up...
...on those eggs!
Oh, Hori-s...
"Coming over today, right?
Get me those eggs asap"
I'm supposed to buy them now?!
And I have to run in this heat?!
Twenty minutes left!
I'll take the shortcut!
Sorry, it's egg time!
Wait, what?!
Egg time?
Man, thanks a ton!
Those rabid housewives were scary...
No more sales for me...
Oh, yeah, uh, I ran into
someone on my way there.
What? Who?! Where?!
That Yuki girl you hang out with.
Oh.
You ran into her dressed like this?
Yeah, but I don't think she knew it was me.
Oh, huh.
Let's dig in!
Look out, don't spill.
Okay.
I kinda don't want anyone else
to see you like this, Miyamura.
Sorry, never mind! Forget I said that.
I forgot to get out drinks. Is barley tea okay?
Are you gonna eat?
Hori-san, I...
When I get to see you like this,
cooking dinner, or getting mad
and yelling really loud...
Like, the fact that you don't care
what your hair looks like at home,
or the way you're kinda brawny, in a good way--
That's enough!
I don't want anyone else
to see this side of you, either.
Neither do I.
It kinda feels like this moment
belongs to me and only me.
Don't say stuff like that, you dummy!
Can I have some, too, please?
Thanks!
Ugh, how can he say something
that cringey with a straight face?!
Does he not realize? Is he that dumb?!
--You dummy. You're such
a dummy! You big dummy!
--I'm a dummy...?
--You dummy. You're such
a dummy! You big dummy!
--You dummy! Dummy, dummy, dummy!
--My sister can't stop saying "dummy"
after she says it once. Watch.
--You dummy! Dummy, dummy, dummy!
--Really?
Dummy, dummy, dummy!
You're right!
Why're you laughing?!
Everyone has a side of them they
don't want anyone to know about.
It's not that I don't like
the way you are at school,
I like this side of you that gets
mad and dresses plain at home.
I think you're way cuter like this.
The two of us ended up sharing
this "secret self" time with each other.
Ugh, whatever, you big dummy.
It's only gonna get hotter from here on out.
Yep.
Wearing this jacket all
the time's gonna be torture.
Yeah, but at least...
Hori-san, I'm in trouble!
We're gonna be swimming in P.E.!
I'm screwed!
Oh, yeah, you're right.
What's wrong with swimming?
Better than making us run a marathon.
Swimming is way worse!
They're gonna see everything!
What do you mean, everythi--
What do I do about these?!
Sometimes I'm not sure if you're incredibly bold
or incredibly stupid.
...at least swimming was optional, huh?
Yeah, for real...
But what if we do have to run a marathon?
I have to wear my jacket!
I'll die of heatstroke!
I don't think they're gonna
make us run a marathon.
Huh. You see the two of
them together a lot lately.
I never expected him to be in the picture.
Hori, lemme see your notes!
Oh, I wanna see, too!
Ugh, fine, but you really need to take your own.
Thanks, Hori!
Popular, huh?
What, uh, what's popular?
Hori.
Oh, yeah. I wish I could
get good grades like her.
Miyamura.
Huh? Wh-What?
You and Hori sure have
been getting along lately.
You two dating?
No! Of course not, that's ridiculous!
Yeah, thought so.
The two of you aren't anything alike.
Yeah, you're right.
We wouldn't make a good couple.
We just don't match up, uh...
Use your words, man!
Don't see those two together often.
Let's go, Hori!
S-Sorry--oh.
What?
Ishikawa-kun, do you have a crush on Hori-san?
Wha--?!
S-So what if I do?!
Wait, really?!
What?!
So that's why you always glare
at me when I'm talking to Hori-san!
W-Well, yeah, I do! So don't...
Sorry, Ishikawa-kun, I didn't know
you had a crush on Hori-san!
Don't announce it to the whole school!
Oh, sorry! Is it still a secret? I'm so sorry!
Yo! What're you guys doing? We gotta go to P.E.!
We're already gonna be late,
so let's take our time heading over.
Actually, here's something I've
been wondering about for a while.
Why are you wearing your winter
uniform in the middle of summer?
Um, uh...
I get cold?
You're sweating buckets.
I know what it's going
to sound like, Ishikawa-kun,
but the only person who's seen me
without a shirt on is Hori-san.
What?! Why?!
Ishikawa-kun, you won't snitch
on me to a teacher, right?
Hell no, I wouldn't!
It'd be a real pain if they found out...
So please don't tell anyone.
What the hell? Are those tattoos?
Wait, they're real?!
Yeah.
Yeah, I can see why you can't wear
our short-sleeved uniform now.
Yeah.
Holy shit.
I totally had you pinned for
the weird, gloomy, otaku type,
but damn, was I wrong.
You're wrong about otaku,
but everything else is spot on.
Now that I'm getting a good look
at him, he does have a nice face.
Though his hair is obnoxious.
Was P.E. in the gym today?
Is this the kind of face Hori's into?
Wh-What?
Whoa! Dude, you have piercings, too?!
Okay, next!
You're a funny guy.
Why get inked or pierced if
you're just gonna end up hiding it?
You know how you do things
in the spur of the moment?
No, I don't.
If you're gonna keep hiding them,
then I won't tell anyone.
Though I wanna know why you and
Hori-san suddenly got all buddy-buddy.
It wasn't sudden.
It happened a little while back, actually.
But I get the feeling
she's just being nice to me.
We're not anything more
than friends, don't worry.
So you don't mind if I ask her out?
Wh-Why are you asking for my permission?
I dunno, just felt like it.
That's up to Hori-san, not me.
I can't believe you skipped P.E., Toru...
You had gym duty, too! Instead,
I had to be the one to clean up!
I said I'm sorry!
Think about what you've done!
I am! I know!
You were hanging out with Toru? That's random.
Oh, yeah. We were just talking.
Hey, why're you avoiding me?
I'm not.
Look me in the eye when you're talking to me!
I-I'm not, it's just...
What is it? Did I do something wrong?
N-No...
Hori!
Huh?
I wanna talk to you later. Is after school okay?
After school?
Oh, but I--
Hori-san, I'll go pick up Sota for you.
Go talk with Ishikawa-kun, okay?
Huh? But...
Oh, she's home!
If they ended up dating,
I'd be a huge third wheel.
Sorry I'm late, Sota!
I'll start dinner in a little bit.
Okay!
Welcome back.
We need to talk.
If she says, "you need to stop
coming over," then that's that.
Toru told me everything.
Oh.
Did you seriously tell him you
don't think we're a good match?
Wha...? Huh?!
Did you really say that you think I'm,
I'm just being nice to you?!
Wait--What about Ishikawa-kun?
Forget about Toru right now!
Huh?!
Did you say that?
Did you tell him all that, Miyamura?!
I did.
That's really what you think this is?
You've been thinking that the
whole time you've been coming over?
No!
No, just... Ishikawa-kun's right,
I'm so gloomy and boring,
I figured I was dragging down
your reputation, or bothering you.
So it's not like I think it's true or anything!
Hori-san?! Why--?
Why...? Why?
Why would you give
a crap about my "reputation"?!
Don't just assume stuff without even asking!
Don't you ever say something
like that again, dummy!
Sorry, Hori-san. I'm really sorry.
Just remembering what you said
makes me so mad!
Wha--? Hori-san?!
If you stopped coming over, Miyamura,
--who'd wake me up when
I fell asleep watching a movie?
--H-Hey--
--who'd wake me up when
I fell asleep watching a movie?
--Or eat your portion of dinner?
--Huh?
--I'd have food left over!
Toru?
I turned him down.
Aww. He seems really sweet, though.
What? You're creeping me out.
Do you have a crush on him or something?
Why don't you guys date?
Oh, I don't think we'd make a good couple.
That's your first reaction?
"You Wear More Than One Face"
Morning, Miyamura.
So, uh, yesterday, I...
You don't have to say it out loud, Ishikawa-kun!
You're such a sweet guy!
What's going on?
No idea. Maybe he's getting asked out?
Who's doing the asking?